What's wrong with the TV.
Nothing, Chris.
All the shows are
in widescreen now.
So you can see all
the stuff on the sides
that you
couldn't before.
ANNOUNCER:
We now return to The Brady Bunch.
See, look.
Here's what you used to see.
Good night, Mike.
Good night, Carol.
And here's the stuff you missed.
♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
Good evening, I'm Tom Tucker.
Diane can't be with us today.
Where is Diane, Ollie?
She dead!
Thanks, Ollie.
Yes, Diane is no longer with us.
She was shot by
an unknown assailant,
after she herself committed
a series of gruesome murders.
I'd like to welcome
our new co-anchor, Joyce Kinney.
Welcome, Joyce.
Thanks, Tom.
Wow, you sound crazy nervous.
In local news,
there was a hit-and-run
by a drunk driver today
at Quahog Park.
Two children are missing.
(gasps)
I was just there.
Oh, boy.
Don't let Brian see this.
It says here that Rush Limbaugh
will be signing books
at the Quahog Mall.
BRIAN (in distance):
I have very good hearing!
(footsteps approaching)
He's awful.
But I thought
Rush Limbaugh is
a fictional character
played by Fred Savage.
Where'd you
hear that?
Fox News.
Then it's a lie.
Everything Fox News
says is a lie.
But this one's true, Mom.
You saw it with your own eyes
and then you reported it
on Fox News.
Even true things, once said
on Fox News, become lies.
Why's Limbaugh
coming here?
Don't they have bookstores
at the Nazi fascist...
fascist fat camp
where he, where he go--
where he, where he is
a counselor?
I tell you what, Brian,
if you want, we'll give you
another crack at that.
This guy single-handedly
set political discourse back
a hundred years.
You know what? I'm
gonna go down there
and give that bastard
Limbaugh a piece of my mind.
But first I'm gonna sit here and
stare at this brown paper bag
I'm pretty sure has food in it.
(sniffing)
PETER:
No!
Ah, oh, well.
Look at him.
His side screwed up our country
for a generation.
I hate everything
about that man.
I'm gonna go
tear him a new one.
I'm gonna go find some
hardcover photography books
of tasteful nudes.
Oh, my God, yes,
that is tasteful.
Hey, my friend,
who should I make this out to?
Listen, Limbaugh, my
name is Brian Griffin,
and I have got
something to say to you.
Our republic has
been bastardized
and royally screwed up
thanks to you jackasses.
You suck!
And you're terrible.
And... and-and
you've div--
you've been divorced
several times.
Yes, uh, valid points
you're raising, my friend,
and I respect you
for raising them.
But may I ask you a question?
Okay.
Have you ever read
anything I've written?
Well, no, I haven't.
But I've read things
other people have written
about the things you've written,
and I do not approve
of the things
I've read from others
about the things
they've read from you.
Not one bit, sir.
For crying out loud, Brian,
read my book.
Judge for yourself.
I'd sooner spend a night
watching European porn.
MAN (moaning):
Provo! Provo!
WOMAN (moaning):
Ah-shnork! Ah-shnork!
Provo!
Ah-shnork!
(loudly):
Provo! Provo!
Ah-shnork! Ah-shnork!
Kaloooooof!
A'gerta!
Stupid right-wing dick.
Yeah, you--
Hey, y-you want to sign my book?
Yeah, you can sign my ass book.
Is what would've been
awesome to say.
Oh, no. It's a multiracial
TV gang, including white guys.
Well, well,
what do we got here?
Let's beat him up,
but not because of his color,
'cause that doesn't
matter to us.
(blows landing)
Wow.
Thanks, Rush.
Ah, it was nothing.
I mean, you'd have
done the same
thing for me.
Uh, yeah, of course.
Hey, you-you
dropped something.
You think you might
give it a read now?
Uh, well...
What-What if I stick a piece
of bologna in the book,
and I don't tell you which page?
Would you read it, then, Brian?
Would you read it to find
the page with the bologna?
Okay, look, I'll read
four pages of your book tonight.
All right?
Four pages.
That's it.
And maybe more
if tonight's episode
of The Office
ends up sucking.
(sighs)
Four pages. Done.
Moving on.
RAINN WILSON:
I know my staplers
by sound and by weight.
And that stapler, good sir,
is a "Schrute."
Ha! Look at John Krasinski
look at the camera.
He can't believe
this guy!
(remote clicks)
Aw, but there were gonna be
more high jinks in Scranton.
(giggles):
Scranton.
Dunder Mifflin.
(giggles)
Funny words
are funny.
Oh, my God.
Rush Limbaugh
was right all along.
Conservative Republicanism
is the answer.
Good. Good for Brian.
Brian, look at this.
Now, this is a
tasteful nude.
It's called "A Saucy Outing
In Tottenham Court Square."
Brian, are you reading the
new Rush Limbaugh book?
Yeah, I picked it up
at the mall yesterday.
I-I can't believe
I'm saying this,
but this might be
the best book I've ever read.
Brian, you got
to be joking.
No, I mean it, Lois.
You know, I've never actually
read any of Limbaugh's stuff,
but this book
makes an excellent case for
personal accountability,
fiscal responsibility
and steak eatership.
But you're a
hard-core liberal.
Rush Limbaugh is a
right-wing extremist.
He stands for
everything you despise.
My loyalty is to reason, Lois.
And as a reasonable person,
I reserve the right
to change my mind
when presented with
new information
that alters my perspective.
And I got to tell you,
I had this guy all wrong.
I mean, some of the stuff
in here is-- hey, bologna!
Thank you, friends.
It's always a pleasure
to meet regular, real Americans.
Love the
Hummer, Rush.
How do you like it?
It is the best.
I'm not saying you'd have to be
gay to drive something else.
But if you drive
something else,
you're probably a guy who likes
to pleasure other men sexually.
(murmurs of agreement)
Hey, it's my new
friend, Brian!
Hi, Rush.
Listen, I-I have to tell you,
I read your book
and it was very persuasive.
I knew you'd like it,
and I'm glad you enjoyed
it, Brian, I really am.
Oh, I-I more than enjoyed it.
Ev-Every page
just spoke to
And-And, you know,
talking to you now, I just,
I-I want to find
the right words
to describe how much
I agree with you.
I got the
words, Brian.
"Thank you, Rush,
for doing my thinking for me,
"'cause I lack
the ability to think
critically and independently."
Yes, that!
You should be proud
of yourself, Brian.
I mean, you sound like
a thoughtful American.
Well, listen, I'd really love
to pick your brain some more
and hear some of
your other thoughts
about what's going on
in this country.
I can do even better
than that, Brian.
Wow.
Never thought
I'd set foot
inside Republican
National Headquarters.
This is amazing.
And it gets better, Brian.
Come on, I'm gonna introduce you
to some of my pals here.
Brian, meet George W. Bush.
Hey, Georgie!
Uncle Rush!
(chuckles):
Hey! Whoo!
You are getting heavy.
I know.
I'm 64 and three-quarters.
You sure are, slugger.
Hey, you got one for me?
What? What are you
talking about?
Oh, come on, Uncle Rush.
I-I don't know what
you're talking about, really.
Come on!
Oh. Wait a second.
Yay! Yippee!
Thanks, Uncle Rush!
Don't tell my dad.
Hey, there, Rush.
How you doing?
Hey, John.
Hey, I'd like you to meet
my friend, Brian.
Brian, John McCain.
Gosh, it sure is
a pleasure, Mr. McCain.
How do you two know each other?
Oh, Rush and I used to
solve mysteries together
back in the day.
I don't understand, John.
The groundskeeper said he saw
the mummy burning the flag.
But mummies don't
hate America.
They sure
don't, Rush.
But Democrats do.
Ruh-roh.
Remocrats.
(teeth rattling)
Oh, it's okay, Hot Dog.
But I think it's time we unravel
the mummy and the mystery.
I don't get
it, John.
How's a pig gonna help
us lure the mummy?
Rush, I've never known
a Democrat to pass up pork.
(snickering)
(moaning)
Gotcha!
Now let's find out
who you really are.
RUSH and JOHN:
It's old man Barney Frank!
And I would have
gotten away with it, too,
if it weren't for you
meddling Republicans.
Thanks for all your help,
Globetrotters.
That was a cold swish.
Put her there.
Aw, no, no, no, no.
(laughter)
Look, Brian, all I'm saying is,
it's not normal for people
to change their political views
so radically overnight.
Lois, no offense,
but you don't exactly know
what you're talking about.
I mean, you're-you're not
exactly a fountain
of political knowledge yourself.
(sighs) You want to know
what I think is happening here?
Oh, this should be
rich and overtaxed.
I think you just got to be
in the "out" group.
Whoever's on top, whoever's
in power, whoever's successful,
you got to be
on the other side
or you don't feel like
the smartest guy in the room.
All you are, my dear,
is a contrarian.
Oh, please, you could
not be more off base.
Oh, yeah? Let me ask, what did
you think of the movie Titanic?
Horrible. One of the
worst movies ever made.
Mm-hmm. How about
Slumdog Millionaire?
Overrated. Just
a terrible movie.
Cocktail.
Actually, not
a bad film.
You know, as classically
structured cinema,
Cocktail was one of the
best films of its era.
You make me sick, Brian.
Look, Lois, if I were you,
I'd stow that attitude,
because Rush Limbaugh is
coming over for dinner tonight.
Lois, this dinner
looks delicious.
Oh, well, thank you.
Dig in, everyone.
Whoa, hang on, hang on.
I think you're forgetting
the grace, Lois.
(sighs)
Dear God who definitely
exists, we, your people,
who have been on this
planet for 6,000 years
and not a second more, wish
to thank you for this bounty,
and for keeping Congress
predominantly white
through Christ
our Lord, amen.
So, Rush, I see you
made it here okay,
driving on roads built with
public funds, by the government.
Yeah, what about
that, Rush?
I guess the government's
pretty good, like Lois says.
Actually, I took the toll roads.
Privately built.
Way smoother than the
crumbling public road system.
Yeah, Lois. Government sucks
at doing stuff.
Oh, no, toll roads
sound great.
Too bad only the very rich
can afford to use them.
I agree with Lois.
Well, maybe more
people could
if the government wasn't taxing
the bajeezus out of them.
Now I agree with Rush.
I'm too a'stupid
to make up my own mind.
Yeah, okay. Whatever
you say, Rush.
So... . nice
weather today.
Yeah,
unseasonably cool.
I guess we can forget
that whole global
warming myth.
Global warming is not a myth,
you son of a bitch!
Look, what the hell
are you so hostile for?
Because you brainwashed
our dog.
Hey, listen,
sister, I just...
(farting)
I'm sorry.
Look, all I did was expose Brian
to a different way of thinking.
He embraced... Oh, God,
I'm gonna move over here.
He embraced it
on his own, Lois.
Well, after Rush
opened my eyes,
I am seeing the world
in a whole new way now.
To quote a famous troublemaker,
"I have a dream..."
♪ I dream of Republicantown ♪
♪ Where men to the
right of the aisle ♪
♪ Don't back down ♪
♪ The streets are aglow
with the smell of apple pies ♪
♪ And babies come out of the
womb in coats and ties... ♪
Nice place, huh, Rush?
It's a paradise, Brian.
♪ Trees grow
from Republican sod ♪
♪ And everyone prays to
a proper right-wing god ♪
♪ Republican Catholics? ♪
♪ Yes, indeed, there are ♪
♪ Republican Muslims? ♪
♪ Well, let's not
go too far ♪
No Muslims?
Nah, too many
tall buildings.
♪ They've outlawed
all abortions ♪
♪ Late or early ♪
♪ It's a sin we can't abide ♪
♪ What if you find
a fetus left abandoned? ♪
♪ We just take it and
we jam it back inside ♪
♪ Oh, yes, 'cause I dream
of Republicantown ♪
♪ The place where the happiest
smile is Cheney's frown ♪
♪ I'll bet you a buck y won't
find a damn thing wrong ♪
♪ 'Cause when
you come down to it ♪
♪ This is where we all belong ♪
Who else lives here?
Oh, big names, Lois.
♪ We're watching
Republican stars ♪
♪ Like sweet Mickey Rourke and
his gorgeous right-wing scars ♪
♪ Chuck Norris is one ♪
♪ And he's got
a right-wing beard ♪
♪ Jon Voight is another ♪
♪ He's just
right-wing weird... ♪
His, uh... his daughter's
pretty hot, though.
At one time, Brian.
At one time.
♪ But how about
global warming? ♪
♪ It's a snow job ♪
♪ By Obama and his crew ♪
♪ But aren't all his
findings backed by science? ♪
♪ Careful, Lois, now
you're sounding like a Jew ♪
Oy.
♪ We dream of Republicantown ♪
♪ Where Clinton is viewed
as a crazy commie clown ♪
♪ A place where America's
growing free and strong ♪
♪ 'Cause when you come down
to it, this is where ♪
♪ We. all... belong. ♪
Well, I got to tell you, I'm
not buying any of this crap.
Rush, we want our dog back.
Whoa, hang on, Lois.
What are you saying?
I don't have a mind of my own?
That's insulting.
And-and you know what?
I don't, I don't
like the way
you've been talking
to Rush this evening.
You know, I-I thought
you were my friends.
But if you can't accept me
now that we disagree
about certain things, then
maybe you aren't the friends
I thought you were.
I'm moving out.
What?!
No!
Again?
I'm gonna go stay
with Rush Limbaugh.
Right, Rush?
Huh?
I'm gonna
stay with you.
Uh... yeah, yeah, sure.
That-That's fine.
Oh, this is a bad idea.
But I guess sometimes
Fox has bad ideas, huh?
Let's all just sit here
for a moment
and remember that
this was a thing.
Morning, Rush.
Hey, thanks again
for letting me stay here.
Oh, it's not really
any trouble, Brian.
What do you figure,
just a few days?
Aw, man, who knows?
It's just so good
to be out of  there.
Hey, you know, I've been
reading all your books
and I so 100% agree with you.
I mean, what is going
on with this country?
I mean, wake up, America.
I mean, these taxes, right?
I mean, am I right?
About the taxes?
You know?
Yeah, taxes are pretty high.
Is-is-is that
a new coffee machine?
Oh, yeah, I took the liberty
of replacing your old one
with a new,
American-made coffee machine.
(electrical crackling)
In fact, I got
you a bunch
of new, topnotch,
American-made stuff.
What else did you buy?
Oh, a couple things:
that light fixture...
new heat regulator
on your stove...
your man-bra...
your garbage disposal...
your dishwasher...
and your new cat.
(cow bellowing):
Moo.
And you're listening to
the Rush Limbaugh Show.
I want to take a moment
to give a shout-out
to my good friend Ken Lay,
faked his own death,
listening in on
a ham radio somewhere
in international waters.
Smooth sailin', Kenny Boy.
Hey, Rush?
Is it okay to
hang out in here?
Wh... All right, fine, just
don't say anything, okay?
So, friends, we were
talking about Nancy Pelosi.
How do we stop her?
How do we stop
the Pelosi agenda--
Hey, I'll tell you how.
You strap her to a board,
put a cloth in her mouth
and pour water over it
to simulate drowning.
Yeah! Small government!
And why don't we take
a short break here, folks.
We'll be right back.
Brian, are you nuts?
What the hell kind of show
you think I'm doing here?.
Wha-What? What are you...
Come on. Pelosi's a monster.
And she's addicted to crack.
Come on, you're with me on this.
Of course she's
addicted to crack,
but you can't just say that.
You got to lead people there
with an intelligent argument
so they arrive at it
on their own.
Hey, come on, man. We got to
tell people how it is.
We got to get them
on board with us.
Brian, look, there is no
victory unless people know why
they were wrong to disagree
with you in the first place.
Boy, do you sound soft.
What the hell's
your problem, Brian?
My-my problem?
My-- right now my
problem seems to be
that I am talking
to a Pelosi-lover.
What?!
Yeah, that's right.
You love Pelosi.
You know what?
It's time for you to go.
Right now.
Hey, fine.
I don't have to sit here and
waste my time with a softie.
You-you call
yourself a Republican?
Republicans don't shy
away from a fight.
And I'm gonna
prove it to you.
Aha!
Who are you?
How did you get in here?
Shut up, Pelosi.
Are you here to take my baby?
No, I'm here to strap
you to a board,
put a cloth in your mouth
and pour water over it
to simulate the
sensation of drowning.
Yeah! Traditional values!
Griffin, you been bailed out.
Oh, Rush, thank God.
Boy, you got down
hereuick.
Yeah, I keep Strom Thurmond's
corpse in the front seat
so I can use
the carpool lane.
Oh.
Okay, well, come
on, let's go home.
t idea.
Tiou to go home.
Home to the Griffins.
Wh... What do you mean?
That's where you
belong, Brian.
You're not really
a conservative.
What are you--
That's not true.
I am conservative.
I support the death penalty
to show people
that killing is wrong.
And that's great, Brian.
Look, I-I make a living
persuading others
to join my side.
But I'd never,
ever want somebody
to be something they're not.
You're a liberal, Brian.
I mean, what about
that four-year-old
that was executed in Texas?
There was a four-year-old
executed in Texas?
Not really, but you see, Brian,
your concern betrays you.
I know your type.
It's not a coincidence
you turned your back
on your democratic principles
just when the Democrats
became the political
establishment.
All you want is something
to fight against.
I mean...
I suppose we shouldn't
be executing children.
You see?
You're not really one of us.
Oh, my God...
Lois was right.
Right there. See, the fact
that you would give a woman
credit for anything...
it means you're
a liberal, Brian.
It's time for you to spread
your two left wings and fly.
Does this-- does this mean
I'll never see you again?
Oh, I'll be around.
Wherever there's
a rich white guy
in need of another tax break,
I'll be there.
Wherever there's
a brain-dead woman
in need
of expensive life support
her husband doesn't want,
I'll be there.
Wherever there's a country
that needs to be invaded
for reasons that don't exactly
pan out, I'll be there, too.
Oh, yes, I will be around.
Hey, Limbaugh.
I think you're a boneheaded,
fascist,
corporate-shilling blowhard.
Look, you little smartass,
I think you are a godless,
socialist, pot-smoking,
maggot-infested member
of the blame-America-first
crowd,
and I think you want
the terrorists to win.
(takes a deep breath)
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru